blessings everyone this is Chris Kendall from the
rb.com registered holistic nutritionist raw food
lifestyle coach and raw Chef today we're making
an amazing recipe from my friend Daniel enzyme
333 his riceless seamos Olive Vera RS let's get
into it baby I like it yeah baby I like it ra all
right so Dan's got a lot of Epic recipes you're
going to want to check him out but what inspired
you to make this one then so I've always wanted
to do a rice wrap but rice isn't completely raw
M so I thought about it and I decided to use ol
vera gel oo cool because it's transparent mhm
and it has pretty much no flavor um sometimes it
can be a little bit bitter but what you do is you
just soak it in water for a while and that bitter
flavor gets released into the water mhm and then
I use seamoss one of my favorite ingredients
MH because again it's clear it doesn't have
much of a flavor and it gels up really nicely
so this recipe would probably be really really
good for your skin because seamoss is a known
collagen Super Booster mhm and they say Alo is
also really really good for your skin topically
and internally by eating it and same with SE
great for your digestive tract too huh so good
for your digestive tract when I ingest sea moss
I can tell that it's super nice on my skin the
next day I feel my skin and I'm just like wow
that's really really nice you seos the same as
Irish moss sea moss and Irish moss are the same
thing yeah there's many different species of
sea moss um this is a golden sea moss from the
Caribbean there's also spaghetti sea moss you
can get purple sea moss and there's the actual
Irish seamos from Ireland and Atlantic Canada
and it looks a little bit different than this
but it's basically the same thing yeah you got
a favorite brand too that we can share and I do
too as well in the notes below hey yeah yeah
I actually sell it myself I distribute it um
Shameless plug we'll put that in there yeah yeah
Moss boss there we go the Moss boss all right so
what are the rough proportions that you use for
this so lately I haven't been measuring it but I
usually just go 5050 50 usually about 70 G of sea
moss and 50 g of Olo and then I just pop it into
the Vitamix or whatever blender you're using yep
you can uh grab a Vitamix with free shipping in
my link below [Music] yo and then you just put
the oloe Vera uh gel in there and then what I
do is I usually fill it with water to about just
below the level of the ingredients yeah I do have
exact measurements in my ebooks yeah which which
ebook uh it's called Edible art okay yeah we'll
have a link for all your ebooks you got like five
good epic books or it six this is a six ebook six
books coming up with a seventh and eighth soon
it'll be a dessert ebook and then just another
ebook full of Entre and and fun meals so yeah I'll
take some of fill this up with the reverse osmosis
water right there yeah we'll start with that and
then okay so I'm just going to pour two piles in
there this will make two really nice clear wraps
we're going to have this for dinner tomorrow huh
yeah tomorrow and this is a really fun recipe
because it's beautiful they're very aesthetically
pleasing and you say it's super easy too right we
just pop the dehydrator and just let it completely
dehydrate yeah don't have to be finicky with the
time and worry about that it can get fully fully
dry yeah it just peels right up off the sheet use
gravity to pull it around here so it can be really
thin hey yeah yeah I let it go pretty thin that's
cool yeah it's kind of like sea snot it's kind of
a mucusy texture yeah it's almost like skin yeah
like it's not surprising that it's such a good
collagen booster because it actually kind of looks
like skin so good to trace minerals too right that
isn't normally found in a lot of produce today
yeah it has something like what 90 some odd
minerals out of the 103 104 or so minerals that
the human body needs y doesn't really have to be
perfect cuz it's going to roll up into a wrap what
do you like to fill them with So lately I've been
doing bloomed forbidden black rice MH I've done
some with kelp noodles colored kelp noodles that
I color with E3 Live Blue Magic blue spirulina mhm
I like to put some peppers in there purple cabbage
but anything that's colorful anything that's going
to really really have that bright color because it
is transparent so you're kind of showing offing
insides you're showcasing the the inard of the r
well you guys are going to have to see what we
decide to put in there for tomorrow that's going
to be in a part two cuz we're going to put these
in the de hydrator and then get on with our even
yep yep this is quick and easy man yeah no it's
a really really easy simple quick recipe and it
looks super cool when you when you have it fully
dehydrated uh how do you store it and like can
it last a little while or do you want to eat it
soon no you could just you could put it in your
cupboard for months and months on end nice I store
them I store them on my shelf yeah I've done the
same with my pizza crusts and they can they can
just chill for quite a while yeah yeah anything
is fully dehydrated is a good uh preservation tool
huh yeah sick let's pop these in the dehydrator go
just slide her in just like that what temperature
I usually do it at about 95 anywhere between 95
and 105 should be good 95 is I think 35 C okay W
you put her low hey I usually do it like 115 to18
been doing 95 lately I don't know why I'm just
keeping the enzy your enzyme man and tomorrow
we'll go to the next part that's right heck yeah
brother all right it's the next day we got these
sheets are we ready to wrap them and roll them
Wrap and Roll let's do it got some filling and
you're making a sauce hey what are you making poon
sauce from my latest ebook Edible art uhhuh so
I've got some dates oh no don't don't tell those
Secrets bro get the book man get the book bro
little bit of avocado action going on here damn
okay when you're ready to use them you just give
it a quick Spritz this is Water by the way yeah
grab the avocado over there fan that out I'm a fan
I'm a fan of this already probably B that much and
then you're going to put orange peppers on there
yes yeah yeah have a salad with a big old salad
too trying to get some some purple cabbage in
there cuz it's so beautiful and we're going
to put some marinated baby king oysters o kind
of marinade you got on that playo it's a chili
powder Ethiopian Burber oh one of my favorites
ever totally little bit of this was going to
use with Bobby but this is the Bubbies beet
horseradish all Bubbies products are raw and
unpasteurized this for flavor and color try not
to put too much in it cuz it is strong oh yeah
that'll be like B oh yeah this will be hitting
in nasal passages opening them up and then some
basil for that authentic Vietnamese salad roll
flavor wow damn damn D these are so good you're
just Folding It wrapping it Fold It Up fold and
wrap try to get it as tight as you can toy like
a toyer yeah it's working pretty good see look
how transparent and how wow cool it shows off
showcases inside beautiful veggies oh my God I
want that in my mouth seriously I'm so excited
we have have this delicious hoisin sauce to dip
it in oh my gosh that looks ridiculous holy cow
wow we taking some nice pictures of that and we
just repeat man you are the freaking Genie this
is going to be a awesome Feast this is Dance Jam
Alive root beer ancient mushroom kind of kuchi
is it a bit it's actually not cucha it's a apple
cider ferment wow so it's it's very legit Ro here
though dang yeah look at this look at this are
you serious you almost can't even see the freaking
sheet so yeah I know it's true it's so translucent
you're saying these things are Hardy like you've
brought them around and like almost like juggled
with them and they they're pretty secure yeah you
could swing it around like a baseball back I've
taken them to the skate park to the bar eaten them
at the bar wow naughty man yeah oh gosh oh gosh
look at that just look at that would you just look
at that seriously where are we going to find you
bro where are we finding you enzyme. 333 on
Instagram yeah yeah um I do have a YouTube channel
starting up it's called enzyme's raw kitchen yeah
it's uh very very new y we got to have like maybe
100 followers dang so and we're both both enzy
and me we're from Saskatoon Saskatchewan here
we've been rocking for a long time in raw food for
like 20 years each it's a yeah freaking skating it
up we'll got a skate we'll put your skate clip
in here too brother it'd be sick straight up
yeah bro nice man yes so give him a check out
definitely subscribe to both his Instagram and
his YouTube and check out all his books he's
got some ridiculous raw masterpieces this is
just a tip of the uh Iceberg or the non rice
wrap BG yeah dang it's like the most nutrient
dense rice paper non rice paper ever too plate
these and smash this back man totally boom wow
wow wow wow brother you are a freaking
magician check this action out oh yeah
and it's salad time as well it's going to be
a feast all right should we smash this back
brother should I give it a try yeah yeah yeah
I'm so stoked since I first seen you posted
what this I've wanted to try it that is so
seriously insane all right I can give it a
proper dip give it a proper dip I can give it
a super dip actually this sauce is so good oh
[Music]
yeah bad ass oh my God it looks
so good this is so legit I'm so
hungry looking at this holy crap join
me join us wow oh yeah yeah [Music]
yeah yeah it's so good the only sad
thing is that we don't have like 65
of these should have made more brother they're so
good two bites up get dipping on there
mhm mhm just like that mhm mhm mhm mhm
mhm that is so proper I hope you love this
video I hope you check out Dan on his Instagram
on his YouTube check out all of his
amazing books everything is going to
be linked below thanks so much brother
this has been an amazing Feast next up
salad time as always wishing you much peace
love and seasonal fruit ress aloe vera seat
Moss reps be sure to check out Dan for more
grab your free raw recipe app available on
iPhone and Android with over 100 free raw
recipes common fruit and vegetable calorie
breakdown freaking rossom food combining
chart shopping cart function and so much more